{"first":{
  "question":"You have decided to move into your own apartment what should you do?",
  "background":"background_10",
  "person":"character_6",
  "face":"face_uncomfortable",
  "fore":"null",
  "answers":["I need to make a change of address notification","I'm not doing anything at all"],
  "I need to make a change of address notification":"ilmoitus",
  "I'm not doing anything at all":"first",
  "I need to make a change of address notificationColor":"green",
  "I'm not doing anything at allColor":"red"},
  "ilmoitus":{
    "question":"Where do you change the address?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["post office","to kela","I make a notice on the trade bulletin board"],
    "post office":"posti",
    "to kela":"ilmoitus",
    "I make a notice on the trade bulletin board":"ilmoitus",
    "post officeColor":"green",
    "to kelaColor":"red",
    "I make a notice on the trade bulletin boardColor":"red"},
  "posti":{
    "question":"How do you notify the mail of a change of address?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_surprised",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["through the postal websites","I go to the post office myself"],
    "through the postal websites":"sivusto",
    "I go to the post office myself":"postikonttori",
    "through the postal websitesColor":"green",
    "I go to the post office myselfColor":"green"},
  "sivusto":{
    "question":"You have completed and submitted the change of address via the mail pages. What next?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_confused",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["transfer of home insurance to a new home","Electricity transmission to a new apartment","providing a new address for the services I use","I will inform the President of my new address"],
    "transfer of home insurance to a new home":"vakuutus",
    "Electricity transmission to a new apartment":"sahko",
    "providing a new address for the services I use":"palvelut",
    "I will inform the President of my new address":"sivusto",
    "transfer of home insurance to a new homeColor":"green",
    "Electricity transmission to a new apartmentColor":"green",
    "providing a new address for the services I useColor":"green",
    "I will inform the President of my new addressColor":"red"},
  "postikonttori":{
    "question":"You go to the post office what do you do?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I ask the staff how I work","I declare that I want to fill in the change of address form","I will play on my phone"],
    "I ask the staff how I work":"tehty",
    "I declare that I want to fill in the change of address form":"tehty",
    "I will play on my phone":"postikonttori",
    "I ask the staff how I workColor":"green",
    "I declare that I want to fill in the change of address formColor":"green",
    "I will play on my phoneColor":"red"},
  "tehty":{
    "question":"You have reported a change of address. What next?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["transfer of home insurance to a new home","Electricity transmission to a new home","providing a new address for the services I use","I will inform the President of my new address"],
    "transfer of home insurance to a new home":"vakuutus",
    "Electricity transmission to a new home":"sahko",
    "providing a new address for the services I use":"palvelut",
    "I will inform the President of my new address":"tehty",
    "transfer of home insurance to a new homeColor":"green",
    "Electricity transmission to a new homeColor":"green",
    "providing a new address for the services I useColor":"green",
    "I will inform the President of my new addressColor":"red"},
  "vakuutus":{
    "question":"You need to change home insurance \/ get home insurance for your new home. How do you handle this?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I physically go to visit the branch of the insurance company","I call the insurance company","I complain on the internet about how hard everything is to handle"],
    "I physically go to visit the branch of the insurance company":"kaynti",
    "I call the insurance company":"soitto",
    "I complain on the internet about how hard everything is to handle":"vakuutus",
    "I physically go to visit the branch of the insurance companyColor":"yellow",
    "I call the insurance companyColor":"green",
    "I complain on the internet about how hard everything is to handleColor":"red"},
  "kaynti":{
    "question":"You arrive at the office what do you do?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_1",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"fore_7",
    "answers":["I wedge myself first","I look forward to my turn and tell the clerk"],
    "I wedge myself first":"viha",
    "I look forward to my turn and tell the clerk":"ohi",
    "I wedge myself firstColor":"red",
    "I look forward to my turn and tell the clerkColor":"green"},
  "viha":{
    "question":"you will be asked to calm down and wait in peace for your own turn",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_1",
    "face":"face_sad",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I obey and look forward to my turn when I tell the clerk","I will not obey but will leave barking at all"],
    "I obey and look forward to my turn when I tell the clerk":"ohi",
    "I will not obey but will leave barking at all":"poissa",
    "I obey and look forward to my turn when I tell the clerkColor":"green",
    "I will not obey but will leave barking at allColor":"red"},
  "ohi":{
    "question":"You have taken care of the matter. What do you do next?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["Electricity transmission to a new apartment","providing a new address for the services I use","I will inform the President of my new address","I move"],
    "Electricity transmission to a new apartment":"sahko",
    "providing a new address for the services I use":"palvelut",
    "I will inform the President of my new address":"ohi",
    "I move":"muutto",
    "Electricity transmission to a new apartmentColor":"green",
    "providing a new address for the services I useColor":"green",
    "I will inform the President of my new addressColor":"red",
    "I moveColor":"green"},
  "poissa":{
    "question":"You didn't get the thing handled what do you do next?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_sad",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I'm trying to transfer the insurance again","Electricity transmission to a new apartment","providing a new address for the services I use","I will inform the President of my new address","I move"],
    "I'm trying to transfer the insurance again":"vakuutus",
    "Electricity transmission to a new apartment":"sahko",
    "providing a new address for the services I use":"palvelut",
    "I will inform the President of my new address":"poissa",
    "I move":"muutto",
    "I'm trying to transfer the insurance againColor":"green",
    "Electricity transmission to a new apartmentColor":"green",
    "providing a new address for the services I useColor":"green",
    "I will inform the President of my new addressColor":"red",
    "I moveColor":"red"},
  "soitto":{
    "question":"You call the insurance company and explain the matter. The clerk asks the security question what are you doing?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["answer the question so I can take care of it","I do not answer the question but I close the call","I ask why the question is asked and I answer it after an explanation"],
    "answer the question so I can take care of it":"kysytty",
    "I do not answer the question but I close the call":"poissa",
    "I ask why the question is asked and I answer it after an explanation":"kysytty",
    "answer the question so I can take care of itColor":"green",
    "I do not answer the question but I close the callColor":"red",
    "I ask why the question is asked and I answer it after an explanationColor":"green"},
  "kysytty":{
    "question":"an clerk inquires about your new apartment?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["answer the questions objectively","I complain to the clerk when he\/she asks too musch","I say I don't have the information right now and I'll call again later"],
    "answer the questions objectively":"ohi",
    "I complain to the clerk when he\/she asks too musch":"kysytty",
    "I say I don't have the information right now and I'll call again later":"poissa",
    "answer the questions objectivelyColor":"green",
    "I complain to the clerk when he\/she asks too muschColor":"red",
    "I say I don't have the information right now and I'll call again laterColor":"yellow"},
  "sahko":{
    "question":"You want the electricity in your new apartment to work. What are you doing?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I use my neighbor's electricity","I call the electricity company","I fill out the forms on the electricity company's website"],
    "I use my neighbor's electricity":"sahko",
    "I call the electricity company":"soitasahko",
    "I fill out the forms on the electricity company's website":"kaavake",
    "I use my neighbor's electricityColor":"red",
    "I call the electricity companyColor":"green",
    "I fill out the forms on the electricity company's websiteColor":"green"},
  "soitasahko":{
    "question":"You call the electricity company and explain the matter. The clerk will ask you about the new apartment",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["You do not answer but you switch off the phone","You answer the questions objectively","You don't answer because you don't know the answers"],
    "You do not answer but you switch off the phone":"poissa",
    "You answer the questions objectively":"ohi",
    "You don't answer because you don't know the answers":"poissa",
    "You do not answer but you switch off the phoneColor":"red",
    "You answer the questions objectivelyColor":"green",
    "You don't answer because you don't know the answersColor":"yellow"},
  "kaavake":{
    "question":"you go to the electricity company's website and there ask for various information about the new apartment",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["You provide all the information","You do not provide your information","You still decide to call the electricity company"],
    "You provide all the information":"ohi",
    "You do not provide your information":"poissa",
    "You still decide to call the electricity company":"soitasahko",
    "You provide all the informationColor":"green",
    "You do not provide your informationColor":"yellow",
    "You still decide to call the electricity companyColor":"green"},
  "palvelut":{
    "question":"You want to provide a new address for the services you use",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_confused",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I go through all my services and call them to tell you my ne address","I will update the information on the website for all services","services may have my old address"],
    "I go through all my services and call them to tell you my ne address":"liittyma",
    "I will update the information on the website for all services":"liittyma",
    "services may have my old address":"liittyma",
    "I go through all my services and call them to tell you my ne addressColor":"green",
    "I will update the information on the website for all servicesColor":"green",
    "services may have my old addressColor":"yellow"},
  "liittyma":{
    "question":"Do you need a home internet connection to the new apartment?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["yes","no"],
    "yes":"valinta",
    "no":"ohi",
    "yesColor":"green",
    "noColor":"green"},
  "valinta":{
    "question":"How do you get a home subscription?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I call the operator and explain the situation","I treat online because I know how to treat it","I handle online even though I don't know how"],
    "I call the operator and explain the situation":"selitykset",
    "I treat online because I know how to treat it":"ohi",
    "I handle online even though I don't know how":"liittyma",
    "I call the operator and explain the situationColor":"green",
    "I treat online because I know how to treat itColor":"green",
    "I handle online even though I don't know howColor":"red"},
  "selitykset":{
    "question":"The clerk will ask you about the new apartment and the subscription for your needs?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["answer all questions to the best of my ability","I don't answer questions but I try to come up with something myself","I will call another operator before making a decision"],
    "answer all questions to the best of my ability":"ohi",
    "I don't answer questions but I try to come up with something myself":"poissa",
    "I will call another operator before making a decision":"valinta",
    "answer all questions to the best of my abilityColor":"green",
    "I don't answer questions but I try to come up with something myselfColor":"red",
    "I will call another operator before making a decisionColor":"green"},
  "muutto":{
    "question":"Once all the arrangements have been made, there is no more relocation left. How do you take care of it?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I order a moving service","I invite my acquaintances to help"],
    "I order a moving service":"muuttopalvelu",
    "I invite my acquaintances to help":"tuttuauttaa",
    "I order a moving serviceColor":"green",
    "I invite my acquaintances to helpColor":"green"},
  "muuttopalvelu":{
    "question":"You call the relocation service and they make your own suggestions regarding the relocation.",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"fore_9",
    "answers":["Just the same thing I advice I do as I want","I listen to suggestions and wonder which ones are right for me","I blindly obey their advice"],
    "Just the same thing I advice I do as I want":"muutetaanpalvelulla",
    "I listen to suggestions and wonder which ones are right for me":"muutetaanpalvelulla",
    "I blindly obey their advice":"muutetaanpalvelulla",
    "Just the same thing I advice I do as I wantColor":"yellow",
    "I listen to suggestions and wonder which ones are right for meColor":"green",
    "I blindly obey their adviceColor":"red"},
  "muutetaanpalvelulla":{
    "question":"The day of moving is coming and you have packed the goods ready for moving in good time, how do you do?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"fore_9",
    "answers":["I open the doors to the migrants and let them take care of migration","I distract myself and confuse everything"],
    "I open the doors to the migrants and let them take care of migration":"muutettu",
    "I distract myself and confuse everything":"muutettu",
    "I open the doors to the migrants and let them take care of migrationColor":"green",
    "I distract myself and confuse everythingColor":"red"},
  "tuttuauttaa":{
    "question":"You call your acquaintances and agree with them how to proceed with the move. How do you work?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"fore_9",
    "answers":["I act as agreed","I do as I please"],
    "I act as agreed":"tuttupalvelu",
    "I do as I please":"tuttupalveluvaarin",
    "I act as agreedColor":"green",
    "I do as I pleaseColor":"red"},
  "tuttupalvelu":{
    "question":"You have prepared everything for the move and the day of the move is coming. How do you work?",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"fore_9",
    "answers":["I move with acquaintances with goods to a new apartment","I let acquaintances change my stuff alone","I act as agreed"],
    "I move with acquaintances with goods to a new apartment":"muutettu",
    "I let acquaintances change my stuff alone":"muutettu",
    "I act as agreed":"muutettu",
    "I move with acquaintances with goods to a new apartmentColor":"green",
    "I let acquaintances change my stuff aloneColor":"red",
    "I act as agreedColor":"green"},
  "tuttupalveluvaarin":{
    "question":"your acquaintances will complain when you have not acted as agreed",
    "background":"background_10",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_sad",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["bark familiar and we change the goods angry","sorry and we change the goods"],
    "bark familiar and we change the goods angry":"muutettu",
    "sorry and we change the goods":"muutettu",
    "bark familiar and we change the goods angryColor":"red",
    "sorry and we change the goodsColor":"green"},
  "muutettu":{
    "question":"everything has now been changed. What are you doing?",
    "background":"background_3",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I unpack the goods and deliver the moving boxes to where they belong.","I leave the goods in boxes","we have already unpacked the goods"],
    "I unpack the goods and deliver the moving boxes to where they belong.":"null",
    "I leave the goods in boxes":"null",
    "we have already unpacked the goods":"null",
    "I unpack the goods and deliver the moving boxes to where they belong.Color":"green",
    "I leave the goods in boxesColor":"yellow",
    "we have already unpacked the goodsColor":"green"}
}